Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/wolfgangleon (LinkedIn) bakrypt.io (Personal) github.com/wolfy18 (Other)

Top Skills

Front-End Development
Python (Programming Language)
React.js

Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Core Principles for Theming in Magento 2 (v2.1)

Algorithmic Trading: Backtest, Optimize & Automate in Python

Mechanical Engineering

Docker for DevOps

Front End Web Development

Wolfgang Leon

Software Engineer

Miami, Florida, United States

Summary

I'm a self-motivated person with a lot of resilience that is always open to new ideas. Coming from a mechanical engineering background and extensive experience in the music industry, I'm a very creative person that thinks outside of the box. I like simple solutions that are easy to communicate in a time effective manner.

Experience

Innovation Refunds
Full Stack Developer
March 2023 - Present (9 months)
Miami, Florida, United States

Wolves Production, LLC Lead Software Engineer / CEO November 2016 - Present (7 years 1 month) Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

BetterNOI

Senior Software Engineer November 2019 - April 2023 (3 years 6 months) Miami, Florida, United States

Moon Media™
Sr Software Developer
April 2017 - June 2019 (2 years 3 months)
Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Global Air Inc Jr Web Developer June 2015 - March 2017 (1 year 10 months) Miami Florida

iAnalyst.com

Web Intern April 2015 - June 2015 (3 months)

Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Miami Catamarans
Sail Instructor
April 2014 - May 2015 (1 year 2 months)
Miami, Florida

Letca Films
Production Assistant
January 2014 - June 2014 (6 months)

Grupo Ingenieria JPX
Operations Supervisor
January 2011 - August 2013 (2 years 8 months)

Education

Thinkful

Web Development, Computer Software Engineering · (2015 - 2015)

Universidad de Carabobo

Mechanical Engineering · (2009 - 2013)